What do you see as adoption today within within the fintech space,
the finance
space?
The adoption today?
I feel like it's going head on into adopting it.
And everyone's really trying to be the competitor
and see what's the best way to get the competitive knowledge.
Because if you're not doing your, your competitor is probably doing it.
And the best way to do that would to incorporate
that early on and just like, adopt it as much as possible.
What I've learned is I don't think AI is going away.
It feels like more and more people have adopted it.
They've, like, build it into their best practices.
There's actually less.
Less people I'm talking to are engineers.
There's like a lot of like outside engineers who are here,
who have, like, vibe coded themselves into a problem and here to learn.
So it's pretty cool.
I think the industry I work in, energy trading, is
I would say it's like a little hesitant in adopting to AI and like new.
It's the new like stuff that comes out.
I think people are just a little more like.
As for believing or trusting the output, but as you started to change
and people are really adapting to that, especially the results that you see
with the Claude model,
or just incorporating that with the new framework
and see how to boost your productivity and everything.
It's been like game changing, and I feel like management is really
starting to adopt that.